{
    "subject": "resource/Uninvited_(video_game)",
    "predicate": "ontology/publisher",
    "object": "resource/Mindscape",
    "human_readable": "Uninvited was published by Mindscape.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9876064658164978,
            "question": "Is 'Uninvited' a publication by Mindscape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9293888211250305,
            "question": "Are there other books published by Mindscape besides 'Uninvited'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7528926134109497,
            "question": "Who published the book 'Uninvited'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6892638206481934,
            "question": "What is the title of the book published by Mindscape?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6118302345275879,
            "question": "Does Mindscape publish fiction or non-fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.609093964099884,
            "question": "What is the name of the publisher that released 'Uninvited'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5316228866577148,
            "question": "What kind of material does Mindscape publish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39429548382759094,
            "question": "Name a book released by Mindscape."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36480340361595154,
            "question": "Which company brought out the book 'Uninvited'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29556548595428467,
            "question": "What is the genre of the book 'Uninvited'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Uninvited was published by Mindscape.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4130_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which company brought out the book 'Uninvited'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4130_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a book released by Mindscape.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4130_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of material does Mindscape publish?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4130_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4130_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents indicate that Uninvited was developed by ICOM Simulations and published by MindScape, supporting the statement that it was published by Mindscape."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}